[music]
>> Okay, hi guys. Welcome, welcome back to
my channel. So, in today's video, this
is going to be my back to school
maintenance
vlog.
And right now, I'm going to go get my
nails done. This is what my nails look
like right now. I got these nails for
like basically a month, I feel like.
And then, the nail design that I'm
getting
Okay, I'm getting these ones.
>> Are you going to the nail salon later?
>> Yeah, I'll take you later.
So, that's the nail design I'm getting.
And then, tomorrow I'm getting my toes
done. And then, tomorrow like at 7:00
a.m. I'm going to get my lashes done.
And then, on
>> The next day?
>> I get my brows done. I get my brows done
today.
Uh
>> Yeah, if I got time.
>> Okay, so might be getting my
eyebrows and 30. My eyebrows are up in
like 30. The day after I get my lashes
done. And then, the 3rd of August, so
like
the next day after that, I'm getting my
hair done at 10:00 a.m. 10:30, one of
those. I forgot.
So,
it was all I needed to get done.
Yeah.
>> Let me tell you about this girl. Maybe I
shouldn't. I met her in Philly and her
name was Brown Sugar. See, we've been
making love constantly. That's why my
eyes always shake. Blood burning. The
way that we kiss is unlike any other way
that I'd be kissing when I'm kissing
what I'm missing. Won't you listen?
Brown Sugar, babe. I get high off your
love. I don't know how to be alone.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Ooh.
>> I'm sugar [music] when you're close to
me.
You love me right down to my knees.
Yeah, whenever you let me hit it.
Sweet like honey when
>> Okay, hey y'all. So, I'm in public
bathroom right now cuz I really really
really really had to pee.
And um nail salon was closing but I had
to finish my nails. But these were my
nails.
And I finished this white.
But this is like my favorite nail set.
Like I love this so much. Like she did
so good.
I tipped her I think $30. I don't
remember. But I tipped her definitely.
They were so cute. I kind of wish they
were sharp but when I go to the nail
salon to get stuff done on my nails they
make them like almond. But when I like
go to like an actual nail tech they're
not actually like
private or I don't know.
But they make them like more sharper. I
kind of wish they were sharper but
they're still so so so so so cute.
>> [laughter and gasps]
>> But I'm not sure when my dad will be
home. I don't really know when he's
coming to pick me up. But I'm pretty
sure he'll be home in a minute.
Should be so
Yeah.
Okay y'all. So, it's currently like 6:00
something in the morning and I'm getting
ready for my lash appointment. I'm
rushing so bad.
I like 3 minutes.
And I got to have the money. Like I Like
I don't have to put out.
My hair
and my bunny.
This is
chapstick.
Um sunscreen. I wish I had sunscreen
there.
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Body oil. I'm rushing so bad.
And then
lotion.
I'm wearing this black shirt and white
Aeropostale like flip flops.
Um
merch boots.
Okay.
>> You had to stay all night for that?
>> No, I didn't have to stay all night. I
just ended up doing it.
>> Oh.
>> Okay, here's my lip liner.
Bring in my airpods.
I don't take it out that often. This is
a mess. I'm rushing so bad.
I should have been gone already, but I
didn't think that.
>> You have two minutes until you go.
>> No, I have zero.
Okay.
I'm bringing a charger.
And then
I'm going to bring
this little blue bag
and bring some stuff
in case I want to do my hair
in the car.
Okay.
That was my rushed get ready with me,
but it's time to go.
See y'all later.
Okay, bye.
Okay, y'all. So, I'm back from my note
Not my note, my lash appointment. And
this is what my lashes look like.
They're a volume set. I don't know what
map she did, so please don't ask. Yeah,
um obviously I couldn't record while
getting them done cuz my eyes had to be
closed the whole time.
But yeah, she charged me $105.
So, that's what they look like and I put
bottom mascara on if you can't tell. I
just wanted to see what it looked like
because you know, school's around the
corner, so I got to see what I like and
what I don't like.
>> Ash.
>> And I'm on the phone with Money right
now. Wait, why is it blinking?
>> Hey guys.
>> Yeah.
>> Hi
>> [laughter]
>> So, yeah, my next maintenance
appointment, whatever, I need to get my
brows and my upper lip
threaded. So, that's the next thing I
got to do.
And then lastly, I'm getting my hair
done.
So, yeah, the lashes are really cute
though.
I didn't think the volume Well, I kind
of knew the volume was going to like,
you know,
look good, but I didn't know how good it
was going to look. I thought it was
going to be like kind of like bigger cuz
I don't think I sent her an inspo Well,
my mom booked the appointment. So, I
don't think she sent her like an inspo
thing, but it turned out cute. And I'm
watching Love Island season 5 in the
background.
So, yeah, I'll see y'all tomorrow when
I'm going to get my brows threaded.
So, yeah. Okay, hey y'all. So, it is
hair appointment day. I'm about to
butcher my hair, but I just got the
shower. It's like early in the morning.
I had to wake up early because I didn't
wash my hair last night, so I had to
wash it today.
But,
yeah, so
Yeah, we're leaving in about like I have
like a
hour. I just put this top on just so
like I have something on, but this is
not what I'm going to wear.
I didn't want to put like what I'm going
to wear on
while I blow dry my hair cuz I know how
hot I can get and I don't want to sweat.
But, yeah, I have the pants on. I'm just
going to be wearing my Glazed Pink Lulu
set.
Yeah. My toes are getting cold. So, I
think my hair is like pretty much
dry enough
for me to, you know, do this. And I need
to look for my AirPods too because I
don't know where they are.
And I need my AirPods. I need them.
Okay, so I think I'm going to just like
blow dry my hair now.
It's pretty like,
you know,
at the right spot to be blow dried for.
I'm pretty sure. I feel like
um
But, I need to go downstairs.
Y'all I to go downstairs and get some
heat protectant, so
BRB. But, I just put the spray protect
the heat the heat protectant in [snorts]
my hair and I went downstairs. I didn't
want to bring you back up cuz
then I'm going to bring you back down.
So, yeah.
I'm really hungry. So, for a good blow
dry, you always need to section your
hair.
Sometimes I don't do that, but this time
I'm going to do it.
So,
I'm going to just section it in four
pieces.
The parts don't got to be straight. I
mean, it's all going to like, you know.
So, we're just going to do it like this.
And then we're going to put this part in
a clip.
I'm I'm really hungry, like and this is
crazy.
Okay.
So,
now we have
the back half.
And I could do half and half or I could
do four sections.
I think for the cleanest,
I need to do four sections.
So, I'm going to do side like this side
this side.
Yeah. This is my blow dryer that I use.
If you were ever wondering, like if you
ever thought I blow dry my hair good and
you want to know what dryer I was, I use
the Wavytalk
blow dryer with this attachment.
So,
yeah, I used to really want like the
like the the brush blow dryer.
You know what I'm talking about?
I'm not going to do this.
But, people say it causes like a lot of
breakage and I
don't want that.
So,
now I'm going to
blow dry my hair
and listen to music while I do it.
Where's my music at? Oh, there it is.
And I'm going to, you know,
fast forward this.
>> Come to me. Skin as caramel
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Okay, so I have completed my blow dry.
So now I'm going to like change into the
the fine jacket.
Time for my AirPods and then leave cuz I
want to leave earlier than we said we
were cuz I'm actually very, very, very
hungry and I want some dumplings. So.
But the blow dry is complete.
Okay, y'all. I'm finna leave, but I
can't show up for you. I'm going to wear
some wearing this
perfume.
Love it so much.
Oh.
This perfume is good.
So yeah, I'm wearing my silver Marc
Jacobs, so
you know, that follows with these, my
silver at Burch.
So let's go.
Okay, y'all. So, I'm at my hair
appointment.
Yeah, I'm getting my hair done. I'm
getting like a flip over.
Kind of, but like not like the curly
one. So,
yeah.
I'm just going to
No.
So, she's providing the bundles. They're
human hair, Vietnamese bundles. I'll put
her the bundles in the description cuz
it's her own hair line. So,
yeah.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay, I'm getting my brows done right
now, but my phone is on 3%, so I can't
really vlog much cuz I need to save for
Apple Pay and my camera's also dead in
the car, so
yeah, but this is one brow done. I did
this one, then my upper lip, and then
yeah.
So, I'll be back later cuz I don't want
my phone to die so I can pay.
Okay, y'all. My camera's literally still
dying, but this is the outcome of my
eye. It's literally dead. But, these are
my eyebrows, so
Okay, y'all, so it's the same day as
literally the hair stuff like red and
everything.
But I have no more maintenance to get
done, so I'm going to end the video up
here. I hope you guys did enjoy this
video, and if you did, make sure you
like, comment, and subscribe. And stay
tuned for the back to school get ready
with me.
I'm not ready to go to school, but I'm
ready for the video, so stay tuned for
that. And yeah.